healthy.net 2013-06-11

# Natural and alternative health and wellness mega-site

Privacy Policy

HealthWorld Online is aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we let you know what information we collect when you use our products and services, and why we collect it.

**What We Collect and Where Do We Collect It**

All users of www.healthy.net are free to explore most of the site without providing any personal information. If you want to access member-only areas, such as the discussion board and commenting on an article, or if you wish to receive our weekly newsletter, Healthy Update, you will be asked to provide your first and last name, email address and zip code. Users of the Healthy Shopping Network (www.healthyshopping.com) provide personal and credit card information to facilitate order fulfillment. Subscribers to the Wellness Inventory (www.WellPeople.com) provide personal and credit card information to facilitate logging to the system and payment processing.

**How HealthWorld Online Uses This Information**

a) Navigational: Our system automatically gathers information about the areas visited by users. To do this, HealthWorld Online logs IP addresses (in other words, the location of your computer on the Internet) for system administration, troubleshooting and to examine overall traffic trends. We do not use any of this navigational data on an individual basis. Nor do we share any of this data with outside companies. We do use navigational information in the aggregate to understand how our users travel around the site as a group to use the services that we of fer. We collect that information so that HealthWorld Online can constantly improve the site. We may also share this statistical information with our partners or other outside companies, but in doing so, we do not disclose individual names or personal navigational information.

b) Personal: When you place an order with any of HealthWorld Online’s Stores (www.healthyshopping.com) or products within Healthy.net, we will ask you for your name, address, phone, and email. In order to process the order. Additional information, such as your preferred means of payment and your shipping address, will be required. We might, from time to time, use the information provided to send you alerts about special offers and to create general customer profiles. You can "opt-out" of receiving such communication at any time, by unsubscribing to the email.

**We Do Not Sell, Trade or Disclose Your Personal Information**

HealthWorld Online does not disclose, share, sell or trade any personal or individual information that it collects to third parties other than in the course of completing a transaction that you have requested or in response to an investigation involving legal matters. While we may provide information regarding site usage to third parties, such as traffic reports and sale information, this information will not include any of your personal information.

**HealthWorld Online Protects Customer Information**

HealthWorld Online uses a secure server for any ordering and credit card information you provide. The servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that safeguards your personal information and guarantees privacy. Our check-out process is certified secure and verified by GeoTrust (www.geotrust.com) and we are an Authorize.net certified merchant.

|   
---  
**"Walking is the best medicine."**  
  
| 

Simply Well

| Explore Healing Music and Sounds  
---  
In the Greek myth of Orpheus, we find a powerful testimony to the power of music. Throughout his journey in the underworld, Orpheus played his lyre and sang. His music pacified the dark forces, bringing...  more  
  
The Nut Gourmet

Cool Quinoa Salad  
---  
A delicious, eye-appealing salad for a hearty family meal or the buffet table, this colorful medley of quinoa, broccoli, black beans, and fresh dill counts on toasted pecans to add the finishing touch....  more  
  
Healthy Hair

Not All Hair Dryers Are Created Equal  
---  
Over the years when consulting with new clients I have often heard the same complaint; "why is my hair so dry?" Nearly always the cause is the result of blow dryer burn, caused by using low-cost made blow...  more
